stream-video-downloader.com 2019-08-17

# Privacy | Stream Video Downloader

## YOUR CONSENT

We respect the privacy of all users of our extension and comply with the User Data Privacy policy for the Chrome Web Store. By using Stream Video Downloader extension for Chrome you consent to this privacy policy.

## DO WE COLLECT PERSONAL OR SENSITIVE DATA? NO.

We do not collect and do not store your personal or sensitive data, including personally identifiable information, browsing history, cookies, cached items, form data, web browsing activity, financial and payment information, health information, authentication information, website content and resources, etc.

## DO WE TRANSMIT PERSONAL OR SENSITIVE DATA VIA INSECURE NETWORKS? NO.

We do not transmit personal or sensitive data (including personally identifiable information, browsing history, cookies, cached items, form data, web browsing activity, financial and payment information, health information, authentication information, website content and resources, etc.) to our servers or to 3rd parties via secure or insecure network. We do not transmit such information at all. The processing is done locally by using an extension API and an origin-isolated extension frame, on your own system (computer).

## DO WE DISCLOSE PERSONAL OR SENSITIVE DATA TO THIRD PARTIES? NO.

We do not sell, trade, collect, store, transmit or otherwise transfer to 3rd parties your personal or sensitive data, including personally identifiable information, browsing history, cookies, cached items, form data, web browsing activity, financial and payment information, health information, authentication information, website content and resources, etc. Your personal or sensitive data remains confidential.

## DO WE COLLECT NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION?

Like most extensions, we may use extension cookies, local storage or other similar technologies that are necessary to the proper functioning of our extension and related services, to store extension settings, enhance your experience, etc.

## WHAT DO WE USE NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION FOR?

Any of the non-personally identifiable information we collect may be used to personalize your experience. This information helps us to better respond to your individual needs and improve our extension, related apps and services. We continually work to improve our extension offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

## DO WE TRANSMIT NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION?

We transmit non-personally identifiable information such as extension version, installation and update events to google analytics service via secure connection.

## CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

> This policy was last modified on **February 20, 2019**

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. info [at] stream-video-downloader [dot] com
